Guide to the Julio Elizalde Papers [Guía a los escritos de Julio Elizalde], 1973-2007 LATINAMER.2013.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writings, 1972-2007; I.
  - Writings, May-August 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Nota [Note], 27 de junio, 1993 [June 27, 1993]; 19.; 1 page
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 2 de julio, 1993 [July 2, 1993]; 20.; 2 pages
    - Análisis especial #23 [Special Analysis #23], 2 de julio, 1993 [July 2, 1993]; 21.; 4 pages
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 3 de julio, 1993 [July 3, 1993]; 22.; 3 pages
    - Nota (Dividida en incisos) [Note (Divided in Sections)], 4 de julio, 1993 [July 4, 1993]; 23.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #2 (Dividido en incisos) [Urgent Message #2 (Divided in Sections)], 8 de julio, 1993 [July 8, 1993]; 24.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial #3 [Special Note #3], 12 de julio, 1993 [July 12, 1993]; 25.; 3 pages
    - Nota especial #5 [Special Note #5], 14 de julio, 1993 [July 14, 1993]; 26.; 3 pages
    - Nota [Note], 18 de julio, 1993 [July 18, 1993]; 27.; 1 page
    - Mensajes urgentes (Dividido en incisos) [Urgent Messages (Divided in Sections)], 21 de julio, 1993 [July 21, 1993]; 28.; 2 pages
    - Mensajes urgentes (Dividido en incisos) [Urgent Messages (Divided in Sections)], 22 de julio, 1993 [July 22, 1993]; 29.; 2 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 31 de julio, 1993 [July 31, 1993]; 30.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 4 de agosto, 1993 [August 4, 1993]; 31.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje al Pentágono [A Message to the Pentagon], 5 de agosto, 1993 [August 5, 1993]; 32.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 7 de agosto, 1993 [August 7, 1993]; 33.; 5 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 9 de agosto, 1993 [August 9, 1993]; 34.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje a la República Popular China, Japón, Estados del Golfo Pérsico, Alemania y el Vaticano [A Message to the People's' Republic of China, Japan, States of the Persian Gulf, Germany, and the Vatican], 13 de agosto, 1993 [August 13, 1993]; 35.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 18 de agosto, 1993 [August 18, 1993]; 36.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente [An Urgent Message], 19 de agosto, 1993 [August 19, 1993]; 37.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #3 final [Urgent Message #3 and Last], 29 de agosto, 1993 [August 29, 1993]; 38.; 4 pages
  - Writings, September-December 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mensaje especial #3 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #3 to the Supreme Leadership], 7 de septiembre, 1993 [September 7, 1993]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #3 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #3 to the Supreme Leadership], 8 de septiembre, 1993 [September 8, 1993]; 2.; 4 pages
    - Post scriptum importante [Important Post Scriptum], 13 de septiembre, 1993 [September 13, 1993]; 3.; 1 page
    - Horas supremas (Dividido en incisos) [Supreme Hours (Divided in Sections)], 2 de octubre, 1993 [October 2, 1993]; 4.; 2 pages
    - Horas supremas (Dividido en incisos) [Supreme Hours (Divided in Sections)], 5 de octubre, 1993 [October 5, 1993]; 5.; 6 pages
    - Un mensaje especial a los teóricos políticos del Army, Navy, Air Force y Marines: Fuerzas en las que está descansando el destino de la humanidad [A Special Message to the Political Theorists of the Army, Navy, Air Force and Marines: Forces in Which the Destiny of Humanity is Resting], 6 de octubre, 1993 [October 6, 1993]; 6.; 8 pages
    - Horas Supremas [Supreme Hours], 9 de octubre, 1993 [October 9, 1993]; 7.; 5 pages
    - Horas Supremas [Supreme Hours], 11 de octubre, 1993 [October 11, 1993]; 8.
    - Mensajes especiales (Divididos en incisos) [Special Messages (Divided in Sections)], 12 de octubre, 1993 [October 12, 1993]; 9.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales (Divididos en incisos) [Special Messages (Divided in Sections)], 14 de octubre, 1993 [October 14, 1993]; 10.; 6 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 15 de noviembre, 1993 [November 15, 1993]; 11.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 22 de noviembre, 1993 [November 22, 1993]; 12.; 3 pages
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of Truth], 27 de noviembre, 1993 [November 27, 1993]; 13.; 4 pages
    - Otro mensaje urgente [Another Urgent Message], 28 de noviembre, 1993 [November 28, 1993]; 14.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 4 de diciembre, 1993 [December 4, 1993]; 15.; 7 pages
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of Truth], 1 de diciembre, 1993 [December 1, 1993]; 16.; 5 pages
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of Truth], 7 de diciembre, 1993 [December 7, 1993]; 17.
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of Truth], 8 de diciembre, 1993 [December 8, 1993]; 18.; 5 pages
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of Truth], 10 de diciembre, 1993 [December 10, 1993]; 19.; 6 pages
    - Análisis especial #1 [Special Analysis #1], 11 de diciembre, 1993 [December 11, 1993]; 20.; 4 pages
    - Análisis especial #3 [Special Analysis #3], 13 de diciembre, 1993 [December 13, 1993]; 21.; 6 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente al leadership [An Urgent Message to the Leadership], 14 de diciembre, 1993 [December 14, 1993]; 22.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje breve al leadership [A Brief Message to the Leadership], 17 de diciembre, 1993 [December 17, 1993]; 23.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente al leadership [An Urgent Message to the Leadership], 17 de diciembre, 1993 [December 17, 1993]; 24.; 2 pages
    - Una semana decisiva [A Decisive Week], 20 de diciembre, 1993 [December 20, 1993]; 25.; 2 pages
    - Una semana decisiva (Segunda parte) [A Decisive Week (Second Part)], 21 de diciembre, 1993 [December 21, 1993]; 26.; 3 pages
    - Nota para ser añadida a semana decisiva parte #3 [Note To Be Added to Part #3 of Decisive Week], 22 de diciembre, 1993 [December 22, 1993]; 27.; 1 page
    - Una semana decisiva (Tercera parte) [A Decisive Week (Third Part)], 22 de diciembre, 1993 [December 22, 1993]; 28.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones [Reflections], 25 de diciembre, 1993 [December 25, 1993]; 29.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones #5 [Reflections #5], 29 de diciembre, 1993 [December 29, 1993]; 30.; 6 pages
    - Reflexiones #6 [Reflections #6], 30 de diciembre, 1993 [December 30, 1993]; 31.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones #7 [Reflections #7], 31 de diciembre, 1993 [December 31, 1993]; 32.; 4 pages
  - Writings, January-April 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Reflexiones #10 [Reflections #10], 3 de enero, 1994 [January 3, 1994]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones #12: Un mensaje al Pentágono [Reflections #12: A Message to the Pentagon], 5 de enero, 1994 [January 5, 1994]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones #13 [Reflections #13], 6 de enero, 1994 [January 6, 1994]; 3.; 4 pages
    - Reflexiones #14: Un mensaje a General Dynamic, Boeing, McDonnell Douglas (Segunda parte) [Reflections #14: A Message to the General Dynamic, Boeing, McDonnell Douglas (Second Part)], 7 de enero, 1994 [January 7, 1994]; 4.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial: El trabajo se paraliza, queda congelado [A Special Message: The Work is Paralyzed, Remains Frozen], 8 de enero, 1994 [January 8, 1994]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje fúnebre, sazonado con sentimientos de alarma [A Funeral Message, Seasoned with Sentiments of Alarm], 24 de enero, 1994 [January 24, 1994]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #4 al poder militar en U.S.A. [Special Message #4 to the Military Poder in the U.S.A.], 6 de febrero, 1994 [February 6, 1994]; 7.; 4 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 7 de febrero, 1994 [February 7, 1994]; 8.; 4 pages
    - Momentos cruciales [Crucial Moments], 12 de febrero, 1994 [February 12, 1994]; 9.; 2 pages
    - *Ultimátum [Ultimatum], 15 de febrero, 1994 [February 15, 1994]; 10.; 6 pages
    - Ultimátum (Segunda parte) [Ultimatum (Second Part)], 17 de febrero, 1994 [February 17, 1994]; 11.; 3 pages
    - El drama en su desenlace [Drama in Its Outcome], 18 de febrero, 1994 [February 18, 1994]; 12.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje urgente [An Urgent Message], 24 de febrero, 1994 [February 24, 1994]; 13.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #8 al poder militar [Urgent Message #8 to the Military Power], 3 de abril, 1994 [April 3, 1994]; 14.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #2 [Special Message #2], 15 de abril, 1994 [April 15, 1994]; 15.; 2 pages
    - Mensaje especial #2 al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #2 to the Supreme Leadership], 20 de abril, 1994 [April 20, 1994]; 16.; 4 pages
  - Writings, July-November 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Sin título [Untitled], 12 de julio, 1994 [July 12, 1994]; 1.; 1 page
    - Horas decisivas #4 [Decisive Hours #4], 19 de julio, 1994 [July 19, 1994]; 2.; 7 pages
    - Estudios políticos [Political Studies], 31 de julio, 1994 [July 31, 1994]; 3.; 7 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 28 de noviembre, 1994 [November 28, 1994]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje crucial #3 (Final) [Crucial Message #3 (Final)], 4 de septiembre, 1994 [September 4, 1994]; 5.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales [Special Messages], 18 de septiembre, 1994 [September 18, 1994]; 6.; 6 pages
    - Mensajes especiales [Special Messages], 19 de septiembre, 1994 [September 19, 1994]; 7.; 8 pages
    - Grito de alarma #4 [Cry of Alarm #4], 16 de octubre, 1994 [October 16, 1994]; 8.; 6 pages
    - Nota especial #4 [Special Note #4], 25 de octubre, 1994 [October 25, 1994]; 9.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas #7 [Decisive Hours #7], 7 de noviembre, 1994 [November 7, 1994]; 10.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #8 [Special Message #8], 28 de noviembre, 1994 [November 28, 1994]; 11.; 5 pages
  - Writings, February-July 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mensaje urgente #5 [Urgent Message #5], 6 de febrero, 1995 [February 6, 1995]; 1.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #19 [Urgent Message #19], 27 de febrero, 1995 [February 27, 1995]; 2.; 1 page
    - Nota urgente #2 [Urgent Note #2], 2 de marzo, 1995 [March 2, 1995]; 3.; 3 pages
    - Urgente nota #10 [Urgent Note #10], 10 de marzo, 1995 [March 10, 1995]; 4.; 6 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #18 [Urgent Message #18], 18 de marzo, 1995 [March 18, 1995]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #26 [Urgent Message #26], 26 de marzo, 1995 [March 26, 1995]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #32 [Urgent Message #32], 1 de abril, 1995 [April 1, 1995]; 7.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje urgente #33 [Urgent Message #33], 2 de abril, 1995 [April 2, 1995]; 8.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 18 de abril, 1995 [April 18, 1995]; 9.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #10 [Special Message #10], 28 de mayo, 1995 [May 28, 1995]; 10.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #14 [Special Message #14], 1 de junio, 1995 [June 1, 1995]; 11.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje especial #15 [Special Message #15], 2 de junio, 1995 [June 2, 1995]; 12.; 4 pages
    - Estudios políticos y sociales #4 [Political and Social Studies #4], 13 de junio, 1994 [June 13, 1994]; 13.; 5 pages
    - Estudios políticos y sociales [Political and Social Studies], 14 de junio, 1994 [June 14, 1994]; 14.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 12 de julio, 1995 [July 12, 1995]; 15.; 8 pages
  - Writings, August-December 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Mensaje breve #7 [Brief Message #7], 15 de agosto, 1995 [August 15, 1995]; 1.; 4 pages
    - Grandes mensajes políticos: Un ciclo histórico tiranizado por el terror, la sangre, la amenaza, la intimidación y actividades subversivas [Grand Political Messages: A Historical Cycle Tyrannized by the Terror, Blood, Threat, Intimidation and Subversive Activities], 2 de septiembre, 1995 [September 2, 1995]; 2.; 6 pages
    - El drama histórico mundial penetra en su desenlace: Acepto todas las responsabilidades que mi capacidad puede asumir [The Historical World Conflict Penetrates in its Outcome: I Accept All of the Responsibilities that I Am Capable of Assuming], 3 de septiembre, 1995 [September 3, 1995]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Sin título [Untitled], 17 de septiembre, 1995 [September 17, 1995]; 4.; 1 page
    - Una semana decisiva [A Decisive Week], 23 de septiembre, 1995 [September 23, 1995]; 5.; 5 pages
    - Crisis #2 [Crisis #2], 11 de octubre, 1995 [October 11, 1995]; 6.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 21 de octubre, 1995 [October 21, 1995]; 7.; 3 pages
    - Crisis #4 [Crisis #4], 13 de octubre, 1995 [October 13, 1995]; 8.; 7 pages
    - Crisis #7 [Crisis #7], 16 de octubre, 1995 [October 16, 1995]; 9.; 5 pages
    - Crisis #8 [Crisis #8], 18 de octubre, 1995 [October 18, 1995]; 10.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje especial #2 [Special Message #2], 22 de octubre, 1995 [October 22, 1995]; 11.; 5 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #10 [In the Hour of Defeat #10], 5 de noviembre, 1995 [November 5, 1995]; 12.; 5 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #21 [In the Hour of Defeat #21], 16 de noviembre, 1995 [November 16, 1995]; 13.; 5 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #23 [In the Hour of Defeat #23], 19 de noviembre, 1995 [November 19, 1995]; 14.; 5 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota [In the Hour of Defeat], 26 de noviembre, 1995 [November 26, 1995]; 15.; 4 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #30 [In the Hour of Defeat #30], 27 de noviembre, 1995 [November 27, 1995]; 16.; 6 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #35 [In the Hour of Defeat #35], 2 de diciembre, 1995 [December 2, 1995]; 17.; 5 pages
    - En la hora de la derrota #39 [In the Hour of Defeat #39], 6 de diciembre, 1995 [December 6, 1995]; 18.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial #5 [Special Note #5], 21 de diciembre, 1995 [December 21, 1995]; 19.; 6 pages
    - Post Scriptum a la "Carta Politica" dirigida al Gen. William Ch. Westmoreland [Post Scriptum to the "Political Letter" Addressed to Gen. William Ch. Westmoreland], 21 de diciembre, 1995 [December 21, 1995]; 20.; 6 pages
    - Nota especial #9 [Special Note #9], 30 de diciembre, 1995 [December 30, 1995]; 21.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial #10 [Special Note #10], 31 de diciembre, 1995 [December 31, 1995]; 22.; 5 pages
  - Writings, January-April 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Nota especial #15 [Special Note #15], 5 de enero, 1996 [January 5, 1996]; 1.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial #20 [Special Note #20], 10 de enero, 1996 [January 10, 1996]; 2.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial #22 [Special Note #22], 12 de enero, 1996 [January 12, 1996]; 3.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 23 de enero, 1996 [January 23, 1996]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial en una hora decisiva [A Special Message in a Decisive Hour], 16 de febrero, 1996 [February 16, 1996]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje especial #2 específicamente dirigido al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #2 Specifically Addressed to the Supreme Leadership], 17 de febrero, 1996 [February 17, 1996]; 6.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #5 específicamente dirigido al Supremo Leadership [Special Message #5 Specifically Addressed to the Supreme Leadership], 21 de febrero, 1996 [February 21, 1996]; 7.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Poder Militar: Ya está redactado el Plan de ataque, que debe recibir el general Barry R. McCaffrey [A Special Message to the Military Power: The Plan of Attack is Already Drafted That General Barry R. McCaffrey Should Receive], 25 de febrero, 1996 [February 25, 1996]; 8.; 3 pages
    - Horas decisivas [Decisive Hours], 28 de febrero, 1996 [February 28, 1996]; 9.; 3 pages
    - Nota [Note], 1 de marzo, 1996 [March 1, 1996]; 10.; 1 page
    - Un mensaje importante al Buró Federal de Investigaciones (F.B.I.) [An Important Message to the Federal Bureau of Investigations (F.B.I.)], 6 de marzo, 1996 [March 6, 1996]; 11.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje importante #3 al Buró Federal de Investigaciones (F.B.I.) [Important Message #3 to the Federal Bureau of Investigations (F.B.I.)], 7 de marzo, 1996 [March 7, 1996]; 12.; 2 pages
    - Mensaje importante #2 al Buró Federal de Investigaciones (F.B.I.) [Important Message #2 to the Federal Bureau of Investigations (F.B.I.)], 7 de marzo, 1996 [March 7, 1996]; 13.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial directamente dirigido al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message Directly Addressed to the Supreme Leadership], 9 de marzo, 1996 [March 9, 1996]; 14.; 4 pages
    - Nota especial [Special Note], 10 de marzo, 1996 [March 10, 1996]; 15.; 1 page
    - Operación Océano Pacífico: Una interpretación histórica destinada a facilitar la reincorporación de Taiwan al continente [Operation Pacific Ocean: A Historic Interpretation Destined to Facilitate the Reincorporation of Taiwan to the Continent], 11 de marzo, 1996 [March 11, 1996]; 16.; 8 pages
    - Mensaje importante #8 al Buró Federal de Investigaciones (F.B.I.) [Important Message #8 to the Federal Bureau of Investigations (F.B.I.)], 15 de marzo, 1996 [March 15, 1996]; 17.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Buró Federal de Investigaciones [A Special Message to the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 27 de marzo, 1996 [March 27, 1996]; 18.; 2 pages
    - Post Scriptum #2: Dirigido a Alemania, la Alemania inmortal [Post Scriptum #2: Addressed to Germany, the Immortal Germany], 6 de abril, 1996 [April 6, 1996]; 19.; 5 pages
    - Un breve mensaje dirigido a General Dynamic, Boeing, McDonnell Douglas, Aramco [A Brief Message Addressed to General Dynamic, Boeing, McDonnell Douglas, Aramco], 9 de abril, 1996 [April 9, 1996]; 20.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales [Special Messages], 19 de abril, 1996 [April 19, 1996]; 21.; 5 pages
  - Writings, May-August 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Un mensaje al Supremo Leadership [A Message to the Supreme Leadership], 13 de mayo, 1996 [May 13, 1996]; 1.; 5 pages
    - Nota [Note], 15 de mayo, 1996 [May 15, 1996]; 2.; 1 page
    - Mensaje especial #3 al Buró Federal de Investigaciones [Special Message #3 to the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 18 de mayo, 1996 [May 18, 1996]; 3.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 29 de junio, 1996 [June 29, 1996]; 4.; 5 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 2 de julio, 1996 [July 2, 1996]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 7 de julio, 1996 [July 7, 1996]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 8 de julio, 1996 [July 8, 1996]; 7.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [A Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 16 de julio, 1996 [July 16, 1996]; 8.; 4 pages
    - Un breve mensaje al Supremo Leadership [A Brief Message to the Supreme Leadership], 19 de julio, 1996 [July 19, 1996]; 9.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje a la División Criminal del Buró Federal de Investigaciones [A Message to the Criminal Division of the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 22 de julio, 1996 [July 22, 1996]; 10.; 4 pages
    - Análisis político: El drama sociopolítico americano. Cuando los Marines fueron asesinados, Beirut, domingo 23 de octubre, 1983, yo consideré que el drama penetraría en su desenlace, pero no fue así. La destrucción del avión de T.W.A., miércoles 17 de julio, ¿precipitará los acontecimientos? [Political Analysis: The American Sociopolitical Conflict. When the Marines Were Assassinated, Beirut, Sunday, October 23rd, 1986, I Considered That the Conflict Would Penetrate in Its Outcome, But It Wasn't Like This. The Destruction of the Plane of T.W.A., Wednesday, July 17th, Will Precipitate the Events?], 25 de julio, 1996 [July 25, 1996]; 11.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial al Supremo Leadership [Special Message to the Supreme Leadership], 23 de julio, 1996 [July 23, 1996]; 12.; 3 pages
    - Atlanta, escándalo mundial [Atlanta, World Scandal], 27 de julio, 1996 [July 27, 1996]; 13.; 2 pages
    - Estados Unidos, una civilización en crisis (Final) [United States, A Civilization in Crisis (Final)], 3 de agosto, 1996 [August 3, 1996]; 14.; 2 pages
    - Análisis: Estados Unidos-República Popular China, Eje político-militar del mundo [Analysis: United States-People's Republic of China, Political-Military Axis of the World], 13 de agosto, 1996 [August 13, 1996]; 15.; 6 pages
    - Un mensaje breve [A Brief Message], 12 de agosto, 1996 [August 12, 1996]; 16.; 4 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 14 de agosto, 1996 [August 14, 1996]; 17.; 5 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 15 de agosto, 1996 [August 15, 1996]; 18.; 4 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 25 de agosto, 1996 [August 25, 1996]; 19.; 4 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 26 de agosto, 1996 [August 26, 1996]; 20.; 6 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 31 de agosto, 1996 [August 31, 1996]; 21.; 6 pages
  - Writings, September-December 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 2 de septiembre, 1996 [September 2, 1996]; 1.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje especial #2 [A Special Message #2], 3 de septiembre, 1996 [September 3, 1996]; 2.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje al Buró Federal de Investigaciones [A Message to the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 7 de septiembre, 1996 [September 7, 1996]; 3.; 3 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Estados Unidos, la crisis de una civilización [At the Heights of World Conflict: United States, the Crisis of a Civilization], 15 de septiembre, 1996 [September 15, 1996]; 4.; 6 pages
    - Un mensaje a los Servicios de Inteligencia del Navy [A Message to the Intelligence Services of the Navy], 3 de octubre, 1996 [October 3, 1996]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Mensaje #2 a los Servicios de Inteligencia del Navy [Message #2 to the Intelligence Services of the Navy], 4 de octubre, 1996 [October 4, 1996]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Un mensaje especial [A Special Message], 6 de octubre, 1996 [October 6, 1996]; 7.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje especial #3 [Special Message #3], 8 de octubre, 1996 [October 8, 1996]; 8.; 3 pages
    - Una hora decisiva [A Decisive Hour], 1 de noviembre, 1996 [November 1, 1996]; 9.; 4 pages
    - Mensajes especiales #2 [Special Messages #2], 30 de noviembre, 1996 [November 30, 1996]; 10.; 5 pages
    - Mensajes especiales #4 [Special Messages #4], 2 de diciembre, 1996 [December 2, 1996]; 11.; 8 pages
    - Mensajes especiales #5 [Special Messages #5], 3 de diciembre, 1996 [December 3, 1996]; 12.; 6 pages
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #5 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #5], 18 de diciembre, 1996 [December 18, 1996]; 13.; 5 pages
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #6 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #6], 18 de diciembre, 1996 [December 18, 1996]; 14.; 6 pages
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #18 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #18], 31 de diciembre, 1996 [December 31, 1996]; 15.; 8 pages
  - Writings, January-April 1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #19 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #19], 1 de enero, 1997 [January 1, 1997]; 1.; 8 pages
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #20 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #20], 2 de enero, 1997 [January 2, 1997]; 2.; 8 pages
    - Reflexiones: Horas decisivas #24 [Reflections: Decisive Hours #24], 6 de enero, 1997 [January 6, 1997]; 3.; 7 pages
    - Nota Breve #4 [Brief Note #4], 10 de enero, 1997 [January 10, 1997]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Nota Breve #5 [Brief Note #5], 11 de enero, 1997 [January 11, 1997]; 5.; 4 pages
    - Nota Breve #7 [Brief Note #7], 15 de enero, 1997 [January 15, 1997]; 6.; 6 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial [At the Heights of World Conflict], 6 de febrero, 1997 [February 6, 1997]; 7.; 7 pages
    - Mensaje especial #7 [Special Message #7], 2 de marzo, 1997 [March 2, 1997]; 8.; 6 pages
    - La hora de la verdad [The Hour of the Truth], 19 de marzo, 1997 [March 19, 1997]; 9.; 5 pages
    - Meses decisivos #2 [Decisive Months #2], 25 de abril, 1997 [April 25, 1997]; 10.; 4 pages
  - Writings, May-August 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sugerencias para una solución [Suggestions for a Solution], 9 de mayo, 1997 [May 9, 1997]; 1.; 8 pages